gamemazing.com 2014-07-02

# Privacy Policy - GameMazing.com: The most amazing Flash and browser games

## Privacy Policy

**GameMazing Games** is owned and operated by **GameMazing LLC**. We may be reached via e-mail at **admin@gamemazing.com**

For each visitor to our web page, our web server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name / IP address, but not the e-mail address (where possible). However, we collect the e-mail addresses of those who register an account with GameMazing or who communicate with us via e-mail.

Any information that we collect is used to improve the content of our web page. It is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. We will never sell, rent, or trade your email address or other personal information. For your security, if you have registered an account with GameMazing, we do not store your account password on our servers.

With respect to advertisements: Our authorized advertising partners offer paid placement ads. Advertising partners may target the placement of ads so that they are relevant to the content of the page, your location, your interests, your demographic information, other personally identifiable information. Advertising partners may store and collect this information through the use of web browser cookies. We have no way of controlling the content of these advertisements on a per-user basis. However, you may opt out of such behavioral advertising by visiting [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and choosing advertisers from which to opt out.

Occasionally we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change in the future, we will post the policy changes to our web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, e-mail us at **admin@gamemazing.com** or check the site periodically for posted updates. As mentioned, we will never sell, rent, or trade email addresse or other personal information.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at **admin@gamemazing.com**. Upon request, we provide site visitors with access to all information (including proprietary information) that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by submitting an e-mail to us at the above address. Consumers may have any information corrected by sending us e-mail.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. If you feel that this site is not following its stated privacy policy, you may contact us via e-mail.
